[MUSIC]
>> Hi everyone, I'm Clive Loesby and I am passionate about changing the world.
One website at a time, as Dale said, I was in a bad car crash a long time ago.
It left us all with life-changing injuries.
And that's why accessibility and website accessibility has become my passion.
The accident also left me with a very bad memory.
So please forgive me for keep looking at my passion. The accident also left me with a very bad memory, so please forgive me
for keep looking at my notes. Okay, does everybody know what a cookie banner is? Those annoying
banners that pop up on a website asking for consent to put cookies into your browser.
It may say something like this website uses cookies to give you the best online experience.
Follow this link to confirm that you can send to this.
Does everyone know what I'm talking about?
Good.
Right.
Now I want you to imagine a different kind of browser.
This one says the following.
This website is designed for white people only.
Follow this link to confirm that you are white. Or this website is for men only. Follow this link to confirm that you are white. Or this website is for men only.
Follow this link to confirm that you are a man. Or this website is for straight people
only. Follow this link to confirm that you are straight. Or even this website is for people who have hair.
Follow this link to confirm you have hair.
Okay, these don't happen in the real world,
but what I don't need to tell you about is another banner that does exist
on over 97% of the world's websites.
This website is for people who are not disabled.
Follow this link to confirm that you are not disabled.
This may not be as apparent as the cookie banner, believe me this banner exists, 97.4% of 1 million website home pages tested last year had detected [BLANK_AUDIO]